A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "Handbook of Antimicrobial Therapy - Dosage Article" Advertising: Package Inserts, 2 of 2 (Box 290, Folder 5)
- "Urinalysis: Microstix and Other Office Tests for Detection of Urinary Tract Infection" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:3, 1974 February 1; 1 of 2 (Box 290, Folder 6)
- "Urinalysis: Microstix and Other Office Tests for Detection of Urinary Tract Infection" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:3, 1974 February 1; 2 of 2 (Box 290, Folder 7)
- "Urinalysis: Microstix and Other Office Tests for Detection of Urinary Tract Infection" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:3, 1974 February 1 (Box 290, Folder 8)
- "Urinalysis: Microstix and Other Office Tests for Detection of Urinary Tract Infection" Sources: "Check Copy" 16:3, 1974 February 1 (Box 290, Folder 9)
- "Urinalysis: Microstix and Other Office Tests for Detection of Urinary Tract Infection" Original Manuscript 16:3, 1974 February 1 (Box 290, Folder 10)
- "Urinalysis: Microstix and Other Office Tests for Detection of Urinary Tract Infection" Reprints 16:3, 1974 February 1 (Box 290, Folder 11)
- "Urinalysis: Microstix and Other Office Tests for Detection of Urinary Tract Infection" Advertising: Package Inserts 16:3, 1974 February 1 (Box 290, Folder 12)
- "New Developments in Pharmacology of Vitamin D" Basic Source Checklist, 16:3, 1974 February 1 (Box 290, Folder 13)
- "New Developments in Pharmacology of Vitamin D" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:3, 1974 February 1; 1 of 2 (Box 290, Folder 14)
- "New Developments in Pharmacology of Vitamin D" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:3, 1974 February 1; 2 of 2 (Box 290, Folder 12)
- "New Developments in Pharmacology of Vitamin D" Sources: "Check Copy", 16:3, 1974 February 1 (Box 291, Folder 1)
- "New Developments in Pharmacology of Vitamin D" Original Manuscript, 16:3, 1974 February 1 (Box 291, Folder 2)
- "New Developments in Pharmacology of Vitamin D" Reprints, 16:3, 1974 February 1 (Box 291, Folder 3)
- "New Developments in Pharmacology of Vitamin D" Advertising: Package Insert, 16:3, 1974 February 1 (Box 291, Folder 4)
- "Anticoagulants in Myocardial Infarction" Basic Source Checklist, 16:4, 1974 February 15 (Box 291, Folder 5)
- "Anticoagulants in Myocardial Infarction" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:4, 1974 February 15; 1 of 2 (Box 291, Folder 6)
- "Anticoagulants in Myocardial Infarction" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:4, 1974 February 15; 2 of 2 (Box 291, Folder 7)
- "Anticoagulants in Myocardial Infarction" Original Manuscript, 16:4, 1974 February 15 (Box 291, Folder 8)
- "Anticoagulants in Myocardial Infarction" Sources: "Check Copy", 16:4, 1974 February 15 (Box 291, Folder 9)
- "Anticoagulants in Myocardial Infarction" Reprints, 16:4, 1974 February 15; 1 of 2 (Box 291, Folder 10)
- "Anticoagulants in Myocardial Infarction" Reprints, 16:4, 1974 February 15; 2 of 2 (Box 291, Folder 11)
- "Interruption of a Drug Regimen before Anesthesia" Basic Source Checklist, 16:4, 1974 February 15 (Box 291, Folder 12)
- "Interruption of a Drug Regimen before Anesthesia" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:4, 1974 February 15; 1 of 2 (Box 291, Folder 13)
- "Interruption of a Drug Regimen before Anesthesia" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:4, 1974 February 15; 2 of 2 (Box 291, Folder 14)
- "Interruption of a Drug Regimen before Anesthesia" Sources: "Check Copy", 16:4, 1974 February 15 (Box 292, Folder 1)
- "Interruption of a Drug Regimen before Anesthesia" Original Manuscript, 16:4, 1974 February 15 (Box 292, Folder 2)
- "Interruption of a Drug Regimen before Anesthesia" Reprints, 16:4, 1974 February 15 (Box 292, Folder 3)
- "Ergotamine and Preparations: Hydergine for Cerebral Arteriosclerosis" Basic Source Checklist, 16:5, 1974 March 1 (Box 292, Folder 4)
- "Ergotamine and Preparations: Hydergine for Cerebral Arteriosclerosis" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:4, 1974 March 1; 1 of 2 (Box 292, Folder 5)
- "Ergotamine and Preparations: Hydergine for Cerebral Arteriosclerosis" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:4, 1974 March 1; 2 of 2 (Box 292, Folder 6)
- "Ergotamine and Preparations: Hydergine for Cerebral Arteriosclerosis" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:5, 1974 March 1 (Box 292, Folder 7)
- "Ergotamine and Preparations: Hydergine for Cerebral Arteriosclerosis" Original Manuscript, 16:5, 1974 March 1 (Box 292, Folder 8)
- "Ergotamine and Preparations: Hydergine for Cerebral Arteriosclerosis" Reprints, 16:5, 1974 March 1 (Box 292, Folder 9)
- "Ergotamine and Preparations: Hydergine for Cerebral Arteriosclerosis" Advertising: Package Inserts, 16:5, 1974 March 1 (Box 292, Folder 10)
- "Imipramine for Enuresis" Basic Source Checklist, 16:5, 1974 March 1 (Box 292, Folder 11)
- "Imipramine for Enuresis" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:5, 1974 March 1; 1 of 2 (Box 292, Folder 12)
- "Imipramine for Enuresis" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:5, 1974 March 1; 2 of 2 (Box 292, Folder 13)
- "Imipramine for Enuresis" Sources: "Check Copy" 16:5, 1974 March 1 (Box 292, Folder 14)
- "Imipramine for Enuresis" Original Manuscript, 16:5, 1974 March 1 (Box 292, Folder 15)
- "Imipramine for Enuresis" Reprints, 16:5, 1974 March 1 (Box 293, Folder 1)
- "Imipramine for Enuresis" Advertising: Package Inserts, 16:5, 1974 March 1 (Box 293, Folder 2)
- "Lactation: Drugs in Breast Milk" Basic Source Checklist, 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 3)
- "Lactation: Drugs in Breast Milk" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 4)
- "Lactation: Drugs in Breast Milk" Original Manuscript, 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 5)
- "Lactation: Drugs in Breast Milk" Reprints, 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 6)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy: Dacarbazine for Malignant Melanoma" Basic Source Checklist, 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 7)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy: Dacarbazine for Malignant Melanoma" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 8)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy: Dacarbazine for Malignant Melanoma" Original Manuscript, 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 9)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy: Dacarbazine for Malignant Melanoma" Reprints, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 10)
- "Effects of Systemic Drugs with Anticholinergic Properties on Glaucoma" Basic Source Checklist, 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 11)
- "Effects of Systemic Drugs with Anticholinergic Properties on Glaucoma" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 12)
- "Effects of Systemic Drugs with Anticholinergic Properties on Glaucoma" Sources: "Check Copy", 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 13)
- "Effects of Systemic Drugs with Anticholinergic Properties on Glaucoma" Original Manuscript, 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 14)
- "Effects of Systemic Drugs with Anticholinergic Properties on Glaucoma" Reprints, 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 294, Folder 1)
- "Haemophilus Influenzae Meningitis Resistant to Ampicillin" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 2)
- "Haemophilus Influenzae Meningitis Resistant to Ampicillin" Reprints, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 3)
- "Imipramine: Tofranil-PM and Antidepressant Therapy" Basic Source Checklist, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 4)
- "Imipramine: Tofranil-PM and Antidepressant Therapy" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:7, 1974 March 29; 1 of 2 (Box 294, Folder 5)
- "Imipramine: Tofranil-PM and Antidepressant Therapy" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:7, 1974 March 29; 2 of 2 (Box 294, Folder 6)
- "Imipramine: Tofranil-PM and Antidepressant Therapy" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 7)
- "Imipramine: Tofranil-PM and Antidepressant Therapy" Original Manuscript, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 8)
- "Imipramine: Tofranil-PM and Antidepressant Therapy" Sources: "Check Copy" 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 9)
- "Imipramine: Tofranil-PM and Antidepressant Therapy" Reprints, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 10)
- "Imipramine: Tofranil-PM and Antidepressant Therapy" Advertising: Package Inserts, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 11)
- "Drug Treatment of Ulcerative Colitis" Basic Source Checklist, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 12)
- "Drug Treatment of Ulcerative Colitis" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:7, 1974 March 29; 1 of 2 (Box 294, Folder 13)
- "Drug Treatment of Ulcerative Colitis" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:7, 1974 March 29; 2 of 2 (Box 294, Folder 14)
- "Drug Treatment of Ulcerative Colitis" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 15)
- "Drug Treatment of Ulcerative Colitis" Adverse Reactions, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 16)
- "Drug Treatment of Ulcerative Colitis" Original Manuscript, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 17)
- "Drug Treatment of Ulcerative Colitis" Reprints, 16:7, 1974 March 29; 1 of 3 (Box 294, Folder 18)
- "Drug Treatment of Ulcerative Colitis" Reprints, 16:7, 1974 March 29; 2 of 3 (Box 295, Folder 1)
- "Drug Treatment of Ulcerative Colitis" Reprints, 16:7, 1974 March 29; 3 of 3 (Box 295, Folder 2)
- "Drug Treatment of Ulcerative Colitis" Advertising: Package Inserts, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 295, Folder 3)
- "Lipids, Drug Reductions: Cholestyramine for Elevated Serum Cholesterol" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:8, 1974 April 12; 1 of 2 (Box 295, Folder 4)
- "Lipids, Drug Reductions: Cholestyramine for Elevated Serum Cholesterol" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:8, 1974 April 12; 2 of 2 (Box 295, Folder 5)
- "Lipids, Drug Reductions: Cholestyramine for Elevated Serum Cholesterol" Sources: "Check Copy" 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 295, Folder 6)
- "Lipids, Drug Reductions: Cholestyramine for Elevated Serum Cholesterol" Original Manuscript, 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 295, Folder 7)
- "Lipids, Drug Reductions: Cholestyramine for Elevated Serum Cholesterol" Reprints, 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 295, Folder 8)
- "Drugs, Injurious Effects (Collagen): Drug-Induced Lupus Syndrome" Basic Source Checklist, 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 295, Folder 9)
- "Drugs, Injurious Effects (Collagen): Drug-Induced Lupus Syndrome" Advertising: Package Inserts, 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 295, Folder 10)
- "Drugs, Injurious Effects (Collagen): Drug-Induced Lupus Syndrome" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:8, 1974 April 12; 1 of 2 (Box 295, Folder 11)
- "Drugs, Injurious Effects (Collagen): Drug-Induced Lupus Syndrome" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:8, 1974 April 12; 2 of 2 (Box 295, Folder 12)
- "Drugs, Injurious Effects (Collagen): Drug-Induced Lupus Syndrome" Original Manuscript, 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 296, Folder 1)
- "Drugs, Injurious Effects (Collagen): Drug-Induced Lupus Syndrome" Reprints, 16:8, 1974 April 12; 1 of 2 (Box 296, Folder 2)
- "Drugs, Injurious Effects (Collagen): Drug-Induced Lupus Syndrome" Reprints, 16:8, 1974 April 12; 2 of 2 (Box 296, Folder 3)
- "Drugs, Injurious Effects (Collagen): Drug-Induced Lupus Syndrome" Advertising; Package Inserts, 1974 April 12 (Box 296, Folder 4)
- "Allergies: Allergic Reaction to Pets" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 296, Folder 5)
- "Allergies: Allergic Reaction to Pets" Original Manuscript, 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 296, Folder 6)
- "Allergies: Allergic Reaction to Pets" Reprints, 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 296, Folder 7)
- "Topical and Systemic Contraceptive Agents" Basic Source Checklist, 16:9, 1974 April 26 (Box 296, Folder 8)
- "Topical and Systemic Contraceptive Agents" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:9, 1974 April 26; 1 of 2 (Box 296, Folder 9)
- "Topical and Systemic Contraceptive Agents" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:9, 1974 April 26; 2 of 2 (Box 296, Folder 10)
- "Topical and Systemic Contraceptive Agents" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:9, 1974 April 26 (Box 296, Folder 11)
- "Topical and Systemic Contraceptive Agents" Reprints, 16:9, 1974 April 26 (Box 296, Folder 12)
- "Topical and Systemic Contraceptive Agents" Original Manuscript and Chart, 16:9, April 26, 1974 and "FDA Approval of Medroxyprogesterone for Contraception, Original Manuscript, 16:11, May 27, 1974, 1974 April 26 1974 May 27 (Box 297, Folder 1)
- "FDA Approval of Medroxyprogesterone for Contraception" Reprints, 16:11, Article in response to "Topical and Systemic Contraceptive Agents", 1974 May 24; 1 of 2 (Box 297, Folder 2)
- "FDA Approval of Medroxyprogesterone for Contraception" Reprints, 16:11, Article in response to "Topical and Systemic Contraceptive Agents", 1974 May 24; 2 of 2 (Box 297, Folder 3)
- "Topical and Systemic Contraceptive Agents" Advertising Package Inserts, 16:9, 1974 April 26 (Box 297, Folder 4)
- "Streptozyme Test" Basic Source Checklist, 16:10., 1974 May 10 (Box 297, Folder 5)
- "Streptozyme Test" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:10, 1974 May 10; 1 of 2 (Box 297, Folder 6)
- "Streptozyme Test" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:10, 1974 May 10; 2 of 2 (Box 297, Folder 7)
- "Streptozyme Test" Original Manuscript, 16:10, 1974 May 10 (Box 297, Folder 8)
- "Streptozyme Test" Reprints, 16:10, 1974 May 10 (Box 297, Folder 9)
- "Streptozyme Test" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:10, 1974 May 10 (Box 297, Folder 10)
- "Anesthetics: Dangers of Innovar" Basic Source Checklist, 16:10, 1974 May 10 (Box 297, Folder 11)
- "Anesthetics: Dangers of Innovar" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:10, 1974 May 10; 1 of 2 (Box 297, Folder 12)
- "Anesthetics: Dangers of Innovar" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:10, 1974 May 10; 2 of 2 (Box 298, Folder 1)
- "Anesthetics: Dangers of Innovar" Original Manuscript, 16:10, 1974 May 10 (Box 298, Folder 2)
- "Anesthetics: Dangers of Innovar" Reprints, 16:10, 1974 May 10; 1 of 2 (Box 298, Folder 3)
- "Anesthetics: Dangers of Innovar" Reprints, 16:10, 1974 May 10; 2 of 2 (Box 298, Folder 4)
- "Anesthetics: Dangers of Innovar" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:10, 1974 May 10 (Box 298, Folder 5)
- "Burns: Silver Sulfadiazine" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:10, 1974 May 10; 1 of 2 (Box 298, Folder 6)
- "Burns: Silver Sulfadiazine" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:10, 1974 May 10; 2 of 2 (Box 298, Folder 7)
- "Burns: Silver Sulfadiazine" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:10, 1974 May 10 (Box 298, Folder 8)
- "Burns: Silver Sulfadiazine" Sources: Check Copy, 16:10, 1974 May 10 (Box 298, Folder 9)
- "Burns: Silver Sulfadiazine" Original Manuscript, 16:10, 1974 May 10 (Box 298, Folder 10)
- "Burns: Silver Sulfadiazine" Reprints, 16:10, 1974 May 10; 1 of 2 (Box 298, Folder 11)
- "Burns: Silver Sulfadiazine" Reprints, 16:10, 1974 May 10; 2 of 2 (Box 298, Folder 12)
- "Burns: Silver Sulfadiazine" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:10, 1974 May 10 (Box 298, Folder 13)
- "Asthma, Drugs for: Metaproterenol" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 1)
- "Asthma, Drugs for: Metaproterenol" Reprints, 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 2)
- "Asthma, Drugs for: Metaproterenol" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 3)
- "Asthma, Drugs for: Metaproterenol" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 4)
- "Obesity: Intestinal Surgery for Obesity" Basic Source Checklist, 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 5)
- "Obesity: Intestinal Surgery for Obesity" Circulation Draft, 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 6)
- "Obesity: Intestinal Surgery for Obesity" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 7)
- "Obesity: Intestinal Surgery for Obesity" Sources; "Check Copy" 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 8)
- "Obesity: Intestinal Surgery for Obesity" Original Manuscript, 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 9)
- "Obesity: Intestinal Surgery for Obesity" Reprints, 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 10)
- "Antiemetics: Drugs for Relief of Nausea and Vomiting" Basic Source Checklist, 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 11)
- "Antiemetics: Drugs for Relief of Nausea and Vomiting" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:11, 1974 May 24; 1 of 2 (Box 299, Folder 12)
- "Antiemetics: Drugs for Relief of Nausea and Vomiting" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:11, 1974 May 24; 2 of 2 (Box 299, Folder 13)
- "Antiemetics: Drugs for Relief of Nausea and Vomiting" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:11, 1974 May 24; 1 of 2 (Box 299, Folder 14)
- "Antiemetics: Drugs for Relief of Nausea and Vomiting" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:11, 1974 May 24; 2 of 2 (Box 299, Folder 15)
- "Antiemetics: Drugs for Relief of Nausea and Vomiting" Sources; "Check Copy", 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 16)
- "Antiemetics: Drugs for Relief of Nausea and Vomiting" Original Manuscript, 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 300, Folder 1)
- "Antiemetics: Drugs for Relief of Nausea and Vomiting" Reprints, 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 300, Folder 2)
- "Antiemetics: Drugs for Relief of Nausea and Vomiting" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 300, Folder 3)
- "Penicillin, New: Amoxicillin" Basic Source Checklist, 16:12, 1974 June 7 (Box 300, Folder 4)
- "Penicillin, New: Amoxicillin" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:12, 1974 June 7 (Box 300, Folder 5)
- "Penicillin, New: Amoxicillin" Sources; "Check Copy", 16:12, 1974 June 7 (Box 300, Folder 6)
- "Penicillin, New: Amoxicillin" Original Manuscript, 16:12, 1974 June 7 (Box 300, Folder 7)
- "Penicillin, New: Amoxicillin" Reprints, 16:12, 1974 June 7; 1 of 2 (Box 300, Folder 8)
- "Penicillin, New: Amoxicillin" Reprints, 16:12, 1974 June 7; 2 of 2 (Box 300, Folder 9)
- "Penicillin, New: Amoxicillin" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:12, 1974 June 7; 1 of 2 (Box 300, Folder 10)
- "Penicillin, New: Amoxicillin" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:12, 1974 June 7; 2 of 2 (Box 300, Folder 11)
- "Gels and Other Topical Corticosteroids" Basic Source Checklist, 16:12, 1974 June 7 (Box 300, Folder 12)
- "Gels and Other Topical Corticosteroids" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:12, 1974 June 7; 1 of 2 (Box 300, Folder 13)
- "Gels and Other Topical Corticosteroids" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:12, 1974 June 7; 2 of 2 (Box 301, Folder 1)
- "Gels and Other Topical Corticosteroids" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:12, 1974 June 7 (Box 301, Folder 2)
- "Gels and Other Topical Corticosteroids" Original Manuscript, 16:12, 1974 June 7 (Box 301, Folder 3)
- "Gels and Other Topical Corticosteroids" Reprints, 16:12, 1974 June 7 (Box 301, Folder 4)
- "Gels and Other Topical Corticosteroids" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:12, 1974 June 7 (Box 301, Folder 5)
- "Cephapirim" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 301, Folder 6)
- "Cephapirim" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 301, Folder 7)
- "Cephapirim" Original Manuscript, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 301, Folder 8)
- "Cephapirim" Reprints, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 301, Folder 9)
- "Cephapirim" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 301, Folder 10)
- "Obesity, Drugs for: Two New Appetite Suppressants" Basic Source Checklist, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 301, Folder 11)
- "Obesity, Drugs for: Two New Appetite Suppressants" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 301, Folder 12)
- "Obesity, Drugs for: Two New Appetite Suppressants" Adverse Effects, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 301, Folder 13)
- "Obesity, Drugs for: Two New Appetite Suppressants" Original Manuscript, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 301, Folder 14)
- "Obesity, Drugs for: Two New Appetite Suppressants" Reprints, 16:13, 1974 June 21; 1 of 2 (Box 301, Folder 15)
- "Obesity, Drugs for: Two New Appetite Suppressants" Reprints, 16:13, 1974 June 21; 2 of 2 (Box 302, Folder 1)
- "Obesity, Drugs for: Two New Appetite Suppressants" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 302, Folder 2)
- "Fluoride for the Prevention of Dental Cavities" Basic Source Checklist, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 302, Folder 3)
- "Fluoride for the Prevention of Dental Cavities" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:13, 1974 June 21; 1 of 2 (Box 302, Folder 4)
- "Fluoride for the Prevention of Dental Cavities" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:13, 1974 June 21; 2 of 2 (Box 302, Folder 5)
- "Fluoride for the Prevention of Dental Cavities" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 302, Folder 6)
- "Fluoride for the Prevention of Dental Cavities" Original Manuscript, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 302, Folder 7)
- "Fluoride for the Prevention of Dental Cavities" Reprints, 16:13, 1974 June 21; 1 of 2 (Box 302, Folder 8)
- "Fluoride for the Prevention of Dental Cavities" Reprints, 16:13, 1974 June 21; 2 of 2 (Box 302, Folder 9)
- "Fluoride for the Prevention of Dental Cavities" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 302, Folder 10)
- "Is All Aspirin Alike? " Basic Source Checklist, 16:14, 1974 July 5 (Box 303, Folder 1)
- "Is All Aspirin Alike? " Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:14, 1974 July 5 (Box 303, Folder 2)
- "Is All Aspirin Alike? " Manufacturer's Replies, 16:14, 1974 July 5 (Box 303, Folder 3)
- "Is All Aspirin Alike? " Sources: "Check Copy", 16:14, 1974 July 5 (Box 303, Folder 4)
- "Is All Aspirin Alike? " Original Manuscript, 16:14, 1974 July 5 (Box 303, Folder 5)
- "Is All Aspirin Alike? " Reprints, 16:14, 1974 July 5; 1 of 2 (Box 303, Folder 6)
- "Is All Aspirin Alike? " Reprints, 16:14, 1974 July 5; 2 of 2 (Box 303, Folder 7)
- "Is All Aspirin Alike? " Advertising; Package Insert, 16:14, 1974 July 5 (Box 303, Folder 8)
- "Sunburns: Sunscreens" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:14, 1974 July 5; 1 of 2 (Box 303, Folder 9)
- "Sunburns: Sunscreens" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:14, 1974 July 5; 2 of 2 (Box 303, Folder 10)
- "Sunburns: Sunscreens" Original Manuscript, 16:14, 1974 July 5 (Box 303, Folder 11)
- "Sunburns: Sunscreens" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:14, 1974 July 5 (Box 303, Folder 12)
- "Dantrolene Sodium for Treatment of Spasticity" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:15, 1974 July 19; 1 of 2 (Box 303, Folder 13)
- "Dantrolene Sodium for Treatment of Spasticity" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:15, 1974 July 19; 2 of 2 (Box 303, Folder 14)
- "Dantrolene Sodium for Treatment of Spasticity" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 304, Folder 1)
- "Dantrolene Sodium for Treatment of Spasticity" Original Manuscript, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 304, Folder 2)
- "Dantrolene Sodium for Treatment of Spasticity" Reprints, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 304, Folder 3)
- "Dantrolene Sodium for Treatment of Spasticity" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 304, Folder 4)
- "Parasitic Infections: Mycanthone for Schistosomiasis" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 304, Folder 5)
- "Parasitic Infections: Mycanthone for Schistosomiasis" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 304, Folder 6)
- "Parasitic Infections: Mycanthone for Schistosomiasis" Adverse Effects, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 304, Folder 7)
- "Parasitic Infections: Mycanthone for Schistosomiasis" Original Manuscript, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 304, Folder 8)
- "Parasitic Infections: Mycanthone for Schistosomiasis" Reprints, 16:15, 1974 July 19; 1 of 2 (Box 304, Folder 9)
- "Parasitic Infections: Mycanthone for Schistosomiasis" Reprints, 16:15, 1974 July 19; 2 of 2 (Box 304, Folder 10)
- "Insect Bites and Stings: Systemic Reactions to Hymenoptera Stings" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 304, Folder 11)
- "Insect Bites and Stings: Systemic Reactions to Hymenoptera Stings" Original Manuscript, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 305, Folder 1)
- "Insect Bites and Stings: Systemic Reactions to Hymenoptera Stings" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 305, Folder 2)
- "Insect Bites and Stings: Systemic Reactions to Hymenoptera Stings" Reprints, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 305, Folder 3)
- "Insect Bites and Stings: Systemic Reactions to Hymenoptera Stings" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 305, Folder 4)
- "Travelers' Warning: Dipyrone in Over-the-Counter Drugs" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 305, Folder 5)
- "Travelers' Warning: Dipyrone in Over-the-Counter Drugs" Manufacturer's Replies, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 305, Folder 6)
- "Travelers' Warning: Dipyrone in Over-the-Counter Drugs" Original Manuscript, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 305, Folder 7)
- "Travelers' Warning: Dipyrone in Over-the-Counter Drugs" Advertising; Package Inserts, 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 305, Folder 8)